Jooheon: Damn it, you overgrown worm!
Jooheon: N-No, not like this!
Jooheon: Kwon, you damn old fool!
How could you do this to me?
Jooheon: How could you do this to me?!
sign: TOMB RAIDER KING
Taejoon: This mission must succeed at all costs.
Taejoon: In return,
I'll give you a reward worthy of it.
Jooheon: There's no way this is how I die!
Jooheon: Jooheon Suh, 38 years old.
Jooheon: Looks like today
Jooheon: is the day I die.
Crow: Good grief, you're loud.
Jooheon: What the hell …?
Crow: Oh? You can hear my voice?
Jooheon: You're not my first talking relic.
Whichever god's trinket you are
Jooheon: get rid of this snake and let me go,
while I'm still asking nicely.
Crow: Do you truly think
you can survive in that body?
Crow: You've been split clean in two.
Crow: At this point, can you even feel pain?
Crow: If I move the snake, will you just
walk out of this place?
Crow: Or do you plan to crawl?
Crow: You're barely holding on to life
by the cheapest of tricks.
Crow: How much longer do you think you have?
Crow: An exceptional talent,
born in the wrong era.
Crow: Now you'll die without ever making proper
use of those little tricks of yours.
Jooheon: Shut up! You know nothing about me.
Jooheon: Do you think
Jooheon: I lived this way, because I wanted to?
Jooheon: Taejoon Kwon, you bastard.
Jooheon: I'll kill you, no matter what it takes!
Crow: Hahaha, how amusing.
Crow: Yes, it would be a waste
to let all that talent die here.
Jooheon: W-What is that?
Jooheon: A crow?
Crow: I will grant you a chance.
Crow: Go and try to claim
the throne of the true king.
Jooheon: Become a king? What?
Jooheon: Why couldn't it be an eagle helping me?
A creepy crow of all things.
Jooheon: Still, it seemed to be
at least a hero-grade.
Jooheon: Maybe... even a god-grade relic?
Jooheon: But it did look like a crow...
Mother: You're just going to let him go?
Mother: He hit my son!
Jooheon: Wait. What's this?
Jooheon: My... My legs!
Mother: This is...
Mother: Oh? Is he out of his mind?!
Jooheon: They're fine.
And more importantly... I'm alive?!
Boy: What's up with that boomer?
Boy: Ugh, this is so annoying.
Mother: See?
There's clearly something up with him.
Mother: So do something!
Jooheon: A police station?
Policeman 1: Hey, hey. Stop muttering
and finish writing your statement.
Policeman 1: I just want your ID.
What's taking you so long?
Mother: I told you he's weird! Goodness.
Policeman 1: I don't have all night.
Jooheon: Ah... yes.
Mother: He looks perfectly normal,
so what's wrong with him?
Jooheon: Is this the crow's doing?
Policeman 1: Name?
Jooheon: Is this a dream? A hallucination?
Jooheon: No, it feels too real.
Policeman 1: I'm asking for your name. Come on!
Policeman 1: I also want to go home, okay?
Policeman 2: Working overtime on
the first day of the year...
Policeman 2: Be damned, 2025...
Jooheon: What?
Jooheon: It's 2025?
Jooheon: How is that possible?
Was I reborn?
Jooheon: No, 2025 was 15 years ago.
Jooheon: Did I... regress into the past? For real?
Crow: Go and try to claim
the throne of the true king.
Mother: Hey, you!
Mother: Why do you refuse to answer?
Mother: And what's with
the muttering and the stupid grin?
Jooheon: That lady... looks familiar.
Jooheon: Now I remember.
Jooheon: That little punk picked a fight
with me first, so I shoved him.
Boy: Are you kidding me? Do you think
I'm a pushover? You started this!
Jooheon: Then he pretended to fall over
and dragged me to the police station.
Boy: Damn, you're pissing me off.
Should I just gouge your eyes out?
Boy: Got a problem? Then fight me!
Mother: You hit my son!
He's a senior in high school!
Mother: Will you take responsibility
for stealing his time?
Jooheon: How did I solve this 15 years ago?
Mother: What if the trauma makes his grades drop?
Jooheon: They demanded a ridiculous settlement,
Jooheon: and I had to get on my knees
and beg for them to lower it.
Jooheon: Back then, I didn't have any money.
Mother: Hello?
Mother: When someone's talking to you, you listen!
Jooheon: Oh? I... blocked it.
Jooheon: Enough is enough, ma'am.
Your son started the fight.
Jooheon: And don't you think you're inflating
the settlement way too much?
Jooheon: Looks like it's true what they say:
The wealthy are the greediest.
Boy: What did you say, you bastard?!
I've had enough of you and your...
Policeman 1: Hey, what do you think
you're doing? Sit down!
Policeman 2: Everybody calm down again, this is not...
Mother: No, my son! Darling, are you all right?!
Jooheon: My body definitely feels lighter.
Mother: Did you see that?
Did you see what he did to my boy?
Jooheon: I haven't caught any
relic-induced illnesses yet either.
Mother: You cannot let him get away with that!
I demand justice!
Jooheon: Are my fighting skills still the same
Jooheon: because I got to keep all of my memories?
Policeman 2: This is a police station!
What do you think you're doing here?
Jooheon: Good. That, at least, works in my favor.
Boy: You just made a big mistake, you little...
Mother: Oh my goodness, are you hurt?
My poor baby...
Mother: You think this is how
things work here, huh?
Mother: Just wait and see.
I'll make you regret this.
Mother: I'm going to call everyone I know and...
Policeman 1: Ma'am, please calm down.
Mother: Calm down?
Do I look like I can just calm down?
Mother: You must be dying to get a criminal
record! Don't even dream of a settlement!
Jooheon: A criminal record?
That stuff won't matter.
Jooheon: Once relics appear, the world
will become a lawless wasteland.
Jooheon: In 2025, massive earthquakes shook
the entire planet, and tombs appeared.
Jooheon: Inside them, relics from myths, legends,
Jooheon: folktales, and popular fiction were found.
Jooheon: They say stories
remembered for ages possess power.
Jooheon: The humans who came to own these relics
were granted all kinds of abilities.
Jooheon: All over the world people
began searching for them.
Jooheon: As luck would have it, I unearthed
the Archaeologist's Relic.
Jooheon: I hit the jackpot.
Jooheon: After gaining vast knowledge
of tombs and relics,
Jooheon: I thought I could
finally turn my life around.
Jooheon: But...
Relic hunter 1: What do you mean we can't enter the tomb?
Soldier 1: TKBM Corporation holds exclusive
excavation rights to these tombs.
Soldier 1: Everyone, please leave.
Relic hunter 2: What? That's ridiculous!
Relic hunter 2: Get out of the way, you clown!
Soldier 1: If you continue to force
your way in, we will open fire.
Jooheon: That's where it all began.
Jooheon: Everything started with
Taejoon Kwon, the chairman of TKBM.
Jooheon: A large number of monopolizers
Jooheon: made it impossible for anyone
but themselves to excavate relics.
Jooheon: Fortunately,
my excavation ability was recognized,
Jooheon: and I was scouted by TKBM Corporation.
Taejoon: Welcome...
Jooheon: I handled all kinds of
dirty jobs for Chairman Kwon.
Taejoon: ...to the team.
Jooheon: Smuggling, theft, spying,
Jooheon: and tomb raiding.
Jooheon: I snuck into tombs that the government
had barred off and smuggled relics out.
Jooheon: Chairman Kwon's success skyrocketed.
TKBM Excavator 2: What a scumbag.
TKBM Excavator 1: Seriously.
TKBM Excavator 2: A bottom-feeder living off a monopolist.
TKBM Excavator 1: Hey, are you pretending not to hear us?
TKBM Excavator 1: If you were born again,
would you still live like that?
Jooheon: As if that would ever happen.
Jooheon: I chose to become Chairman Kwon's dog,
Jooheon: putting up with
every insult and humiliation.
Jooheon: And in the end...
Julian: C-Captain, this is a trap!
Jooheon: Once relics appear, the world
will become a lawless wasteland.
Jooheon: It's good that I can still fight,
but that alone won't be enough.
Jooheon: Time to gather everything
I need to start excavating...
sign: [TOMB RAIDER JOOHEON SUH]
Jooheon: What's that?
Why are there words floating in the air?
Jooheon: Great. I must be losing it.
sign: [TOMB RAIDER JOOHEON SUH]
A LOUSY THIEF WHO CAN'T EVEN USE A SHOVEL.
Jooheon: Only a relic could pull
this kind of crap...
Jooheon: Hey, you feathered rat!
Come out right now!
Jooheon: Are you hiding somewhere and watching me?!
sign: TOMB RAIDER BASIC SKILLS (1/4)
SPY  [RANK F]
DETECT EVERYTHING IN A 1-METER RADIUS.
Jooheon: A skill window?
Jooheon: Spy? Rank F?!
Jooheon: That damn crow!
Jooheon: Is my life a game now?
sign: NEW QUEST
UNLOCK ALL 4 SKILLS OF A TOMB RAIDER.
AWAKEN THE FOUR HIDDEN SKILLS WITHIN YOU
TO BECOME A FULL-FLEDGED TOMB RAIDER.
Jooheon: What? Activate four skills?
Jooheon: Will you look at that?
Now there's even a quest?
Policeman 1: What is it now? Keep it down, will you?
Jooheon: Ah... sorry.
Jooheon: Am I... the only one who can see it?
Speaking of which...
Jooheon: Everything within a
one-meter radius is crystal clear.
Jooheon: That's the ability
the Archaeologist's Relic gave me.
Jooheon: The relic is gone,
but the ability remains?
Jooheon: Does that mean I can now
see all of my skills this way?
Jooheon: Wait, if this is one out of four,
that means there's three more.
Jooheon: Well, we're off to a great start.
Jooheon: But what's that crow after?
Jooheon: Relics don't usually help humans...
Geonwoo: Hey, Jooheon!
sign: SERVING AND PROTECTING OUR COMMUNITY
Geonwoo: Bad luck, huh?
That high schooler is a repeat offender.
Geonwoo: He's the one
who should be sitting in that cell.
Geonwoo: Don't worry, I'll take care of everything.
Jooheon: Thanks, Geonwoo.
Geonwoo: Did you hit your head on something?
Geonwoo: Jooheon Suh is thanking me?
What's gotten into you?
Geonwoo: You sound like a totally different person.
Geonwoo: Guess the holding cell
really scared you, huh?
Jooheon: Detective Geonwoo Kim.
Jooheon: Growing up at the orphanage,
he was always there for me like family.
Geonwoo: Come on now. Let's go.
Jooheon: He still looked so young 15 years ago.
Jooheon: Geonwoo, have there been
any strange activities lately?
Jooheon: People being possessed
or anything involving superpowers?
Geonwoo: What are you talking about?
Are you sure you're all right?
Jooheon: You need to see a shaman
for these kinds of things.
Geonwoo: Well, sometimes it does feel
like my wife has superpowers.
Geonwoo: How does she always find my secret stash?
Jooheon: Looks like relic users
haven't appeared yet.
Geonwoo: Go home and get some rest.
You had a rough day.
Jooheon: Tombs should have appeared here and there,
but no relic users as of now.
Jooheon: This is the perfect time to make a move.
Jooheon: The problem is money.
Jooheon: Most of the early relics
were in Europe and the Americas.
Jooheon: But I need plane tickets...
Kyungtae: Hey, Jooheon Suh.
Kyungtae: Why the hell are you
wandering around instead of working?
Jooheon: There's my cash cow.
Jooheon: Kyeongtae Park.
Jooheon: A local thug who runs a small gallery
with his older sister, Kyungjoo Park.
Jooheon: Back in school, I was desperate for money,
so I worked part-time for them.
Jooheon: For a pathetic wage, I put up
with their punches and worked like a dog.
Seungwoo: Why aren't you answering,
you little shit?!
Seungwoo: Do you need a beating to come to
your senses? Lower your damn eyes, you...
Jooheon: You morons go and
tell your boss that I'm done.
Jooheon: So hand over
my back pay and severance.
Kyungtae: All right, you bastard.
Let's settle this today!
Thug 1: B-Boss!
Thug 2: What's with this guy?
Y-You go and help him!
Thug 1: Shut up! Rush at him all at once!
Thug 2: My eyes... My nose...
Thug 2: My eyes! My eyes!
Thug 2: My nose! My nose!
Seungwoo: W-What's going on? How is this possible?
Jooheon: Well, that's 15 years
of accumulated skills for you.
Jooheon: I'm missing the strength, though.
Jooheon: I need to finish this quickly.
Jooheon: Is that all? Finished already?
Kyungtae: You ungrateful brat!
This is how you repay our kindness?!
Seungwoo: B-Boss, be careful with that knife!
Seungwoo: What if he gets seriously hurt and...
Kyungtae: Will you shut up?! Who cares?!
Jooheon: Oh? This knife... is a relic.
Jooheon: Why does that lowlife have it?
Jooheon: Well, I guess it's not all that surprising.
Jooheon: Some relics slip out of
their tombs and hide in human society.
Kyungtae: You think you're tough? Die, you bastard!
Jooheon: Either way, that thing is mine now.